<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on ALPHASE</title>
    <link>https://example.org/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on ALPHASE</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© BuddyHeartO</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 11:42:00 +0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://example.org/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Home Lab</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/home-lab/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 11:42:00 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/home-lab/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;background&#34;&gt;Background&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I had a friend whom I lent my old laptop to. It was a Thinkpad X260 that I bought 4-5 years ago. He gave it back to me because of some issues: keyboard is typing on its own, and it is not responsive. In the first place, soon after I got the laptop first hand 4 years ago, I replaced the keyboard. Its layout was Japanese and I felt uneasy typing with Japanese keyboard. So, I put the old keyboard sparepart in a box, used the laptop for a while, even broke the &lt;em&gt;backspace&lt;/em&gt; key, and lent it to my friend. As soon as he returned the laptop, I checked and confirmed the issue. I wanted to tinker in Linux and that kind of stuff so I thought that using that old laptop would be a good idea. I replaced the keyboard to the old Japanese keyboard, and unfortunately the issue remained. &amp;ldquo;It must be the connector&amp;rdquo;, I thought. Even though I had a full-size membrane keyboard laying around, I still didn&amp;rsquo;t think using a &lt;strong&gt;portable&lt;/strong&gt; laptop with a &lt;strong&gt;full-size&lt;/strong&gt; keyboard is a good idea, it would occupy much space.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My First Post</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 23:41:55 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;and&#34;&gt;And&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Aloha! You can call me &lt;em&gt;Daniel&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Danil&lt;/em&gt;, or &lt;em&gt;Budi&lt;/em&gt;, if you know me from campus. I am now writing a blog because I&amp;rsquo;m anxious and lonely. I want the word to hear me&amp;hellip;maybe someone like &lt;em&gt;you&lt;/em&gt; stumble across this blog among thousands of other blogs on the internet.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;frontdoor-carpet&#34;&gt;Frontdoor Carpet&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Welcome to my blog! I named it &lt;em&gt;Alphase&lt;/em&gt;, a combination of words &lt;em&gt;alpha&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;phase&lt;/em&gt;. &lt;em&gt;Alpha&lt;/em&gt; means &lt;em&gt;start&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;the first (version)&lt;/em&gt;, or &lt;em&gt;socially dominant person/animal&lt;/em&gt; (the latter is not quite like me). &lt;em&gt;Phase&lt;/em&gt; means &lt;em&gt;chapter&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;stage&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;point&lt;/em&gt;. I personally chose this name because I want to make this blog as a starting point for others to get to know me better. Well, I have to admit that I&amp;rsquo;m an introverted, awkward, and reserved person and I can&amp;rsquo;t convey my feeling fully by talking to other people. So if you read this first post now and other posts, I&amp;rsquo;ll be happy because my voice is finally heard.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
